We're at call four of the modern specialty,
killing and torturing, needing for the March 1st, 2021,
to the invitation by Pastor of the Modern Franchist Church.
They have a prayer here.
Let's go up there and get ready to begin.
All right, let's pray together.
Thank you so much for this evening and for this gathering of our city council.
I pray for wisdom in this room, and I pray to you and empower our leaders
with the ability to make clear decisions,
and I pray that you would bring unity into our town
where we would help us to recognize the gifts and the blessings that you give in us,
and help us to be generous towards others in the way that you have been generous towards us.
And we thank you so much for your love and your grace.
I'm going to ask you all this in Jesus' name, Timmy.
I pledge allegiance to the light of the United States of America,
and to the United States of America,
and it is a little bit of liberty and justice to us.
We have a lot of four book and book for us,
get the personal answers.
Let's have five, through the place.
That's a good one.
Five, five, five, six of the business of being in the business of closing this agenda.
That would trust the community of the mountains,
and eight to join the Muslims.
Five, five, six, five, six, five.